Louisa: Hi! I'm Louisa.
I’m in New York.
I’m from England, but I’m here to learn about the life of a tour guide.
Peter Greenwald is a New York tour guide.
He lives in a small apartment in Brooklyn.
He usually gets up at eight o’clock.
Peter has a big breakfast.
He usually has fruit and cereal,
and sometimes he has an omelette.
He leaves the house at nine o’clock.
Peter works for a company called Real New York Tours.
His tours always begin in Times Square.
Every morning, he goes there by subway.
Peter usually arrives at about nine forty-five.
He meets his group and tells them about the tour.
At ten o’clock, the tour begins.
Peter takes them to places of interest all around Manhattan.
They have lunch in Greenwich Village.
Peter usually has a real New York pizza.
The tour ends in Wall Street.
After work, Peter takes the subway back to Brooklyn.
Then he relaxes.
He usually reads a book.
Sometimes, he watches TV.
He goes to bed at about eleven o’clock.
He needs to sleep.
Every day he walks about six miles!
Peter is an excellent tour guide;
he loves his job, and he loves New York.